{
    "subject": "resource/Pentair",
    "predicate": "http://purl.org/dc/terms/subject",
    "object": "resource/Category:Swimming_pool_equipment",
    "human_readable": "Pentair's subject is Category:Swimming pool equipment.",
    "questions": [
        {
            "score": 0.9322953224182129,
            "question": "What is the overall purpose of Pentair's swimming pool equipment?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.9144610166549683,
            "question": "Can you give some examples of Pentair's swimming pool equipment?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.8219688534736633,
            "question": "Who are some of Pentair's competitors in the swimming pool equipment market?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.8147525787353516,
            "question": "Is Pentair involved in any other industries besides swimming pool equipment?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.7167961001396179,
            "question": "How has Pentair contributed to the evolution of swimming pool technology?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.618204653263092,
            "question": "What are some common uses for Pentair's products?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.422759473323822,
            "question": "What type of products does Pentair manufacture?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.2621465027332306,
            "question": "What are some of the key features that distinguish Pentair's products from others in the market?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.24055591225624084,
            "question": "Where might you find Pentair products sold?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.16743037104606628,
            "question": "Does Pentair offer any maintenance or repair services for its products?"
        }
    ],
    "google_pages": [
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Pentair's subject is Category:Swimming pool equipment.",
            "html": "dbpedia_5260_0.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Where might you find Pentair products sold?",
            "html": "dbpedia_5260_1.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=What are some of the key features that distinguish Pentair's products from others in the market?",
            "html": "dbpedia_5260_2.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=What type of products does Pentair manufacture?",
            "html": "dbpedia_5260_3.html"
        }
    ],
    "selected_docs": [
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_5260_10.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_5260_100.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_5260_121.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_5260_153.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_5260_21.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_5260_26.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_5260_32.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_5260_35.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_5260_39.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_5260_65.txt"
        }
    ],
    "final_question": "Is true?",
    "responses": {
        "gemma2": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{'output': 'yes'}\n```  \n"
        },
        "llama3.1": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "Here is the response:\n\n`{'output': 'yes'}`\n\nThe documents provided describe Pentair as a company that specializes in innovative and dependable swimming pool and spa equipment, highlighting its products such as pumps, heaters, LED lighting technology, chlorine generators, automatic cleaners, and electronic control systems. This information supports the claim that Pentair's subject is Category:Swimming pool equipment."
        },
        "qwen2.5": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{\"output\": \"yes\"}\n```\n\nThe provided documents discuss various aspects of Pentair, including its role as a global leader in swimming pool and spa equipment, emphasizing innovation, reliability, energy efficiency, and a range of solutions. This information supports the statement that Pentair's subject is Category:Swimming pool equipment."
        },
        "mistral": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": " {\"output\": \"yes\"}"
        }
    },
    "need_tiebreaker": false,
    "tiebreakers_responses": {
        "qwen2.5:14b": {},
        "llama3.1:70b": {}
    },
    "final_decision": 1,
    "actual_decision": 1,
    "analysis": {
        "stratum": "Popular",
        "topic": "-"
    },
    "errors": {}
}